Guide to the Annette Weiner Papers MC 152
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Reprints
  - NYU & Other- Hexter, J.H.: Fernand Braudel and the Monde Braudellien, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - NYU & Other- Hughes, Diane Owen: From Brideprice to Dowry, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - NYU & Other- Irvine, Judith T.: How not to Ask a Favor in Wolof; Wolof Speech Styles and Social Status, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - NYU & Other- Jameson, Fredric: Postmodernism and Consumer Society, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - NYU & Other- Karp, Ivan: New Guinea Models in the African Savannah; Living with Spirits of the Dead; Reading the Nuer, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - NYU & Other- Keesing, Roger M.: Kwaio Kindreds; On Descent and Decent Groups, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - NYU & Other- Kroeber, A.L.: Classificatory Systems of Relationship, 1909; The Role of Style in Comparative Civilizations (1963), undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - NYU & Other- Kydd, Rachael M.: Reason and Conduct in Hume's Treatise, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - NYU & Other- Leach, Edmund: Political Systems of Highland Burma, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - NYU & Other- Leach, Foss and Davidson, Janet: Archeological Studies of Pacific Stone Resources, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - NYU & Other- Leacock, Eleanor B.: Interpreting the Origins of Gender Inequality: Concepturl and Historical Problems; Myths of Male Dominance, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - NYU & Other- Leacock, Seth: The Ethnological Theory of Marcel Mauss, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - NYU & Other- Levi- Strauss, Claude: The Culinary Triangle; Anthropology: Its Achievement and Future; Structuralism and Ecology, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - NYU & Other- Levy-Bruhl, H.: Marcel Mauss, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - NYU & Other- Mc Cabe, Joseph: The Taint in Politics, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7838 0
  - NYU & Other- Medick, Hans: The Proto- Industrial Family Economy, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - NYU & Other- Meillassoux, Claude: Essai d' Interpre'tation du Phe'nome'ne E'conomique dans les Socie'te's Traditionnelles d'auto-subsistance, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - NYU & Other- Meinecke, Friedrich: Machiavallism: the Doctrine of Raison D' Etat and Its Place in Modern History, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - NYU & Other- Mitchell, William E.: Theoretical Problems in the Concept of Kindred, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - NYU & Other- Mosko, Mark S.: Motherless Sons: 'Divine King' and 'Partible Persons' in Melanesia and Polynesia, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - NYU & Other- Murdock, George Peter: Anthropology's Mythology, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - NYU & Other- Naquin, Susan: Funeral in North China: Uniformity and Variation, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - NYU & Other- Needham, Rodney: Alliance and Classification among the Lamet; Polythetic Classification, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - NYU & Other- Nielsen, Donald A.: Robert Hertz and the Sociological Study of Sin, Expiation and Religion, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - NYU & Other- Parmentier, Richard J.: House Affiliation Systems in Belau; Times of the Signs; Semiotic Meditation; Diagrammatic Icons and Historical Processes in Belau, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - NYU & Other- Radcliffe-Brown, A.R.: Structure and Function in Primitive Society: Chapter 6, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - NYU & Other- Ranger, T.O.: From Humanism to the Science of Man: Colonialism in Africa and the Understanding of Alien Societies, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - NYU & Other- Ricoeur: Problematic: The Placing of Freud (Book I), undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - NYU & Other- Rosaldo, Michelle Zimbalist: Woman, Culture, and Society, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - NYU & Other- Sahlins, Marshall D.: The Segmentary Lineage: An Organization of Predatory Expansion; On the Ideology and Composition of Descent Groups, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - NYU & Other- Scheffler, H.W.: Ancestor Worship in Anthropology: or, Observations on Descent and Descent Groups, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - NYU & Other- Scott, Joan W. and Tilly, Louise A.: Women's Work and the Family in 19th Century Europe, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - NYU & Other- Shapiro, Warren: Patri-Groups, Patri-Categories, and Sections in Australian Aboriginal Social Classification; Semi-Moiety Organization and Mother-in-Law Bestowal in Northeast Arnhem Land, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - NYU & Other- Sider, Gerald M.: Christmas Mumming and the New Year in Outport Newfoundland; The Ties That Bind, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - NYU & Other- Silverstein, Michael: The Value of Objectual Language, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - NYU & Other- Simmel, Georg: The Sociology of Sociability, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - NYU & Other- Simpson, George: A Durkheim Fragment, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - NYU & Other- Small, Cathy A.: The Powers and Limitations of Women's Cooperative Organizations in Tonga; From the Ground Up, undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - NYU & Other- Stocking, George W., Jr.: Essays on Museums and Material Culture, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - NYU & Other- Thompson, E.P.: Time, Work-Discipline, and Industrial Capitalism; The Moral Economy of the English Crowd in the Eighteenth Century, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - NYU & Other- Topley, Marjorie: Cosmic Antagonisms: A Mother-Child Syndrome, undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - NYU & Other- Turner, Terence S.: Parsons' Concept of Generalized Media of Social Interaction and Its Relevance for Social Anthropology; The Social Skin, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - NYU & Other- Valeri, Valerio: Death in Heaven: Myths and Rites of Kinship in Tongan Kingship, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - NYU & Other- Van der Leeden, A.C.: Thundering Gecko and Emu: Mythological Structuring of Nunggubuyu Patrimoieties, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - NYU & Other- Wade, John: The Extraordinary Black Book, 1831 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - NYU & Other- White, Merry I.: Japanese Education: How do they do it?, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - NYU & Other- Winn, Marie: The Loss of Childhood, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Bibliography, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7839 8
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Aibel, Robert, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Albers, Patricia and Medicine, Beatrice, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    General
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Aldridge, Alfred Owen, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Allen, Peter S. and Others, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Andrew, Dudley, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Asch, Timothy and Marshall, John, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Asch, Timothy and Chagnon, Napoleon, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Bateson, Gregory, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Becker, Howard S., 1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Bennett, Tony, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Blumler, Jay G. and Gurevitch, Michael, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Boyle, Deirdre, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Brantlinger, Patrick, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Cambridge University Journal, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Cavell, Stanley, undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Cinema Texas Program Notes, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Collier, John Jr., 1975 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Cook, David, undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Curling, Chris J., 1978 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Cussler, M., 1948 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Dunlop, Ian, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Eaton, Mick, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Eaton, M. and Ward, I., 1976 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Edgerton, Gary and Pratt, Cathy, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Feld, Steve, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Fiske, J. and Hartley, J., undated (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Forman, Denis, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Fussell, Paul, undated (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Ginsburg, Faye, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Ginsburg, Faye, undated (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Granada Television of England, undated (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Hall, Stuart, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Heider, Karl G.: Fieldwork with a Cinema, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Heider, Karl G.: The Dani of West Irian, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Henley, Paul, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors A-I: Henny, Leonard M., 1986 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Jacknis, Ira S., 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 0405 7840 6
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Koch, Gerd, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Kottak, Conrad, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Krouse, Susan Applegate, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Lajoux, Jean-Dominque, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Lobo, Susan, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Loizos, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: MacDougall, David, 1969-1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Marshall, Lorna, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Mead, Margaret, 1936-1976 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Myerhoff, Barbara and Ruby, Jay, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Myers, Fred, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Nichols, Bill, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Peterson, Nicholas, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Reichlin, Seth, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Roddick, Nick, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Rouch, Jean, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Ruby, Jay, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Schneider, Mary Jane, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Singer, Andre, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Sontag, Susan, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Sorrenson, E. Richard, undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Springer, Claudia, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Steiger, Ricabeth and Taureg, Martin, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Strathern, Andrew, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Weiner, Annette B., undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Wood, Michael, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Woodhead, Leslie, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Woth, Sol, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - NYU & Other- Articles related to Films: Authors J-Z: Young, Colin, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Bibliography, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7841 4
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Anderson, Johannes C., 1941 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Angas, George French, 1847 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Archey, Gilbert, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Barrow, T.T., 1956-1959 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Best Elsdon (1 of 5), 1898-1917 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Best, Elsdon (2 of 5), 1898-1931 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Best, Elsdon (3 of 5), undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Best, Elsdon (4 of 5), undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors A-Best: Best, Elsdon (5 of 5), 1924 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Biggs, Bruce, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7842 2
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Buck, Peter H., 1921-1925 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Carkeek, W., 1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Colenso, W., 1880 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Craik, George, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Davis, Charles Oliver, 1855 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Donne, T.E. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Downes, T. W., 1932 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Golson, Jack, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Graham, George, 1905 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Gudgeon, W.E., 1905-1907 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Hongi, Hare, 1896 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Houston, John (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Jackson, Michael, 1968-1972 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: Johansen, J. Prytz, 1954-1958 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors Be-J: "Greenstone", 1907-1967 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors K-R, undated (Box 36)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7843 0
  - Articles related to Maori: Authors S-Z, undated (Box 37)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7844 8
  - Articles related to Gender: Authors A-F, undated (Box 38)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7845 5
  - Articles related to Gender: Authors G-M, undated (Box 39)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7846 3
  - Articles related to Gender: Authors N-Z, undated (Box 40)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7847 1
  - Articles related to Culture & Anthropology, undated (Box 41)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7848 9
  - Articles related to Oceania: Oceania Archeology & Bibliography on Oceania, undated (Box 42)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7849 7
  - Articles related to Oceania: Polynesia & Polynesian Voyage, undated (Box 43)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7850 5
  - Articles related to Polynesia-- Hawaii: Authors A-J, undated (Box 44)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7851 3
  - Articles related to Polynesia-- Hawaii: Authors K-Z, undated (Box 45)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7852 1
  - Articles related to Polynesia-- Polynesia Explorers: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 46)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7854 7
  - Articles related to Polynesia-- Fiji: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 47)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7855 4
  - Polynesia-- Tahiti: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 48)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7856 2
  - Articles related to Polynesia-- Samoa: Authors A-K, undated (Box 49)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7857 0
  - Articles related to Polynesia-- Samoa: Authors L-Z, undated (Box 50)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7858 8
  - Articles related to Polynesia-- Tonga, Tikopia, and Small Islands: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 51)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7859 6
  - Articles related to Polynesia-- Tikopia and Small Islands: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 51A)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7860 4
  - Articles related to Melanesia- MANA and On Malinowski: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 52)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7861 2
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Trobriands: Authors A-J, undated (Box 53)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7862 0
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Trobriands: Authors K-O, undated (Box 54)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7863 8
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Trobriands: Authors P-Z, undated (Box 55)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7864 6
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- New Guinea: Authors A-D, undated (Box 56)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7865 3
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Papua New Guinea: Authors A-D, undated (Box 57)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7866 1
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Papua New Guinea: Authors E-G, undated (Box 58)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7867 9
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Papua New Guinea: Authors H-L, undated (Box 59)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7868 7
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Papua New Guinea: Authors M-Pn, undated (Box 60)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7869 5
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Papua New Guinea: Authors Po-R, undated (Box 61)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7870 3
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Papua New Guinea: Authors S, undated (Box 62)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7871 1
  - Articles related to Melanesia-- Papua New Guinea: Authors T-Z, undated (Box 63)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7872 9
  - Articles related to Cloth & Arts: Authors A-I, undated (Box 64)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7873 7
  - Articles related to Cloth & Arts: Authors J-Z, undated (Box 65)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7874 5
  - Articles related to Exchange(Money): Authors A-L, undated (Box 66)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7875 2
  - Articles related to Exchange (Money): Authors M-Z, undated (Box 67)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7876 0
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors A-Bei, undated (Box 68)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7877 8
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors Bej-De, undated (Box 69)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7878 6
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors Dd-F, undated (Box 70)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7879 4
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors G-He, undated (Box 71)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7880 2
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors Hd-K, undated (Box 72)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7881 0
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors L-Mo, undated (Box 73)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7882 8
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors Mp-R, undated (Box 74)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7883 6
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors S, undated (Box 75)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7884 4
  - Miscellaneous Articles: Authors T-Z, undated (Box 76)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7885 1
  - Articles related to Postmodernism: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 77)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7886 9
  - Articles related to Arts: Authors A-G, undated (Box 78)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7887 7
  - Articles related to Arts: Authors H-Z, undated (Box 79)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7888 5
  - Articles related to Australia and Kinship: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 80)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7889 3
  - Articles related to Indonesia and Greece: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 81)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7890 1
  - Articles related to Collecting, Perception, Property, and Theory: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 82)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7891 9
  - Articles related to On Malinowski: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 83)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7892 7
  - Articles related to Oedipus, Munn, Nancy D., and Powell, H.A.: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 84)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7893 5
  - Articles related to Freeman, Derek, Mead, Margaret, and Freeman/Mead Debates: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 85)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7894 3
  - Articles related to Kwakiutl and Virgin Birth: Authors A-Z, undated (Box 86)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7895 0
- Series V: Conferences
  This series contains materials related to professional conferences.
  - A Malinowski Retrospective, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7896 8
  - Archives Conference, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Australian Conference, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Bellagio Conference, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Burg Wartenstein Conference, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - European Conference, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Cloth and the Organization of Human Experience I, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7897 8
  - Cloth and the Organization of Human Experience II, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Cloth and the Organization of Human Experience III, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Cloth and the Organization of Human Experience IV, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Divine Ruler Conference I, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7898 4
  - Divine Ruler Conference II, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Divine Ruler Conference III, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Divine Ruler Conference IV, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7899 2
  - Divine Ruler Conference V, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Divine Ruler Conference VI, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Divine Ruler Conference VII, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Divine Ruler Conference VIII, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Divine Ruler Conference IX, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Divine Ruler Conference X, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Divine Ruler Conference XI, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Divine Ruler Conference XII, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Divine Ruler Conference XIII, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - The Family on the Threshold of the 21st Century, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7900 8
  - Film Conference, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Finland Conference, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Folk Culture in Texas: Preservation & Presentation, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Frazer, J. G.: His Life and Work, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - The Gift Conference I, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - The Gift Conference II, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - The Gift Conference III, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Humanities Seminar for Visiting Scholar, NYU, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - I.U.A.E.S. Intercongress Amsterdam, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Kula Conference, University of Cambridge, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7901 6
  - Kula Conference, Virginia I, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Kula Conference, Virginia II, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Leiden Conference: The Gender of Power, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Material Culture Conference, Santa Fe, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7902 4
  - Material Culture Conference I, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Material Culture Conference II, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Mead-Freeman Conference: Samoa and the Freeman-Mead Controversy in America, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Melanesia Conference, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Pacific Science Congress XIV, XV, and XVII, 1979, 1983, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7903 2
  - Pacific Basin Health Issues Conference, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 2)